80bola.com 2015-03-15

# Live Score service (powered by Livescores.cc) - Privacy Policy

We do not collect your personal information when you simply browse our website. During the process of delivering an information to you via our website, Livescores.cc does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address etc...

For the time beeing we do not require personal information at all.

However, Livescores.cc may or may not obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example), or what screen resolution do you use.

The information collected by Livescores.cc via [Google Analytics](http://google.com.80bola.com/intl/en/analytics/tos.html)* is used for the purpose of improving your browsing experience on our website. In some cases, you may voluntarily provide personal information in response to a survey, registering for an online competiton, signing up for a newsletter or personalizing your Livescores.cc pages.

If this does occur, Livescores.cc will never, under no circumstances, use such personal information for any purposes other than the ones you have provided them for. 

Livescores.cc, as well as most sites on the Internet, uses "cookies" to enhance your experience on the web.  
Livescores.cc cannot use these cookies to personally identify you in any way.

A cookie is a small piece of information that is sent to your browser from a World Wide Web Server.   
This block of data can be anything, a unique user ID generated by the server, the current date and time, the IP Address of where the browser is logged onto the net or any other chunk of data that you want.

After a browser receives a cookie it will then send that cookie to the server that set it whenever it is appropriate and required/requested. The browser will only send the cookie to the server that originally set it.  
This means that the server can't tell if your browser has cookies that other sites have sent.

An HTTP Cookie cannot be used to get data from your hard drive, get your email address or steal sensitive information about your person.  
The Livescores.cc Web Server(s) will send a Cookie to a Client system when our adserver serves an ad in order to record unique ID associated with this ad so that should you decide to click on the ad, your browserknows which advertiser's web page to redirect you to.

We may or may not also use cookies to enhance your experience on our website (personalization,...). We believe cookies to be harmless, and will eventually be to everyone's benefit (end users, as well as site builders).

If you do not want the benefit of cookies, there is a simple procedure to manually delete your cookies. Please consult your web browser's Help documentation for more information.

Read more about our [**Cookies Policy**](http://livescores.cc.80bola.com/privacy/cookies/)
